Here we go... Upcomi has begun. This time, we have Ichika Arisawa of Juice Juice and Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume. 23's Rio Sakurai.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the up-front group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Now then, I would like to start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs. I, Arisa, am currently on tour.
I always get my hair done at Dambara Hair Salon. I always get my hair done at Dambara Hair Salon, which is run by Dambara Ruru, and also by Risa, who is run by Irie Risa,
I always went to Dambara Beauty Salon, which is run by Dambara Ruru, or Risachi Beauty Salon run by Irie Risa, and they always did my hair, but I thought this was a bad idea,
I didn't practice, but I decided to try it once by myself, and I was able to do it,
I tried it once, and I was able to do it. I tried it once, and I was able to do it. I can't do two difficult hairstyles, but I can do a ponytail and a half updo now.
But if I can do those two, I can appear in anything. I think I am very talented,
Akari Endo contacted me and said she would like to see your half-twins, but I can never do half-twins.
I can never do half-twins. I like the way they are parted in the middle.
I'm going to practice a little bit before the concert.
I want to practice a little before the concert and make Akari happy.
I want to see it too.
I'll send you a picture.
Yay, I'll be waiting.
I've been playing games in my free time before the concert.
I've been playing Word Wolf and Werewolf,
In Word Wolf, if you don't talk, the game stops, so in a way, I'm honing my talk ability.
That's great.
That's what I thought.
I'm pretty weak at werewolf, by the way.
I look like I'm really good at it.
Really?
It shows on my face. Very much so.
Expressive.
That's right. People say I have a tell-tale face.
I get told I have a werewolf face.
That's right.
I want to improve my werewolf skills, and I'm learning and having fun with the other members.
It's great. I'd like to learn more about werewolf, and I'm having fun doing it with the other members while I'm learning.
Let's start with the first one.
BEYOOOOONDS Motome yo... Unmei no Tabibito San Vocal Recording
Here is Momohime Kiyono's vocal recording of BEYOOOOONDS's latest single, "Motome yo... Unmei no Tabibito San.
Do you think the monitors are okay?
Yes, they are fine.
Yes, let's take a shot then.
Let's sing in a languid, fun way.
Okay, then, take one.
Please.
It doesn't make sense. I mean, when is this ever useful?
Well, not much, actually. But it doesn't hurt to try.
But it doesn't hurt to try. - Can't we make it more quirky?
I don't see the point. When is it going to help?
Not much, really. But it doesn't hurt to try.
No, they're all so hard.
When does it help?
Well, not much, really
But it doesn't hurt to try
That's good, that's good, that's good
That's it, that's it, that's it
Let's try the B melody.
I'll see you in 25 minutes
But it can't hurt to try
What do you do?
Add, add, add. -Low, low, diagonal.
Add, add, add. One minute.
200 meters, then divide by the distance.
That's what the second half looks like.
The first two lines are just to change the mood, so...
It's like thinking time.
What do you do, add, add, add, add, add, add, add, add, add.
Add, add, add. One minute, look.
200 meters. Continue. Divide by the distance.
I know I'm going to the extreme, but let's try something like that.
But it can't hurt to try.
Don't move out, move out, pull back, don't fold, move out, move out, move out, one step at a time, see?
200 meters away... divide the distance by the distance...
Okay, let's continue with the chorus.
Lively, yes!
Everybody is a traveler of destiny
Everyone is a traveler of destiny, coincidences are blooming, let's call forth a miracle
I'm led by the hand that I'm guided by the hand that I'm guided by the hand that I'm guided by the hand that I'm guided by
Everyone is a traveler of destiny Let's seek more of life Let's seek more of happiness
I'm in a great mood Even if I'm not in a cat
Let me out, let me out, it's easier I've been having so much fun I want you to laugh
Life's all about wanting more, more, more, more
Yeah, the last line was good.
Yes.
Shall we take two lines of "If you add and divide..."?
Yes.Yes, I am.
I'm just getting tired of the throat, you know.
Yes.
You have to get it together.
Then I'll take it in two lines.
I'm counting on you.
OK.
Okay.
Then, let's go next.
Then, we'll continue with the lines, right?
Yes.
I feel like I'm cutting too much off, so I can't make it in time.
I see.
A-Chome and B-Chome are 5 km apart.
Nishida-san walks 50 meters per minute from A-Chome.
I stop where there is a point there.
50 meters.
And Ms. Yutaka Sato rides her bicycle from B-Chome at 150 meters per minute and leaves at the same time?
Yes. There, take a break.
Yes.
When they leave?
They're meeting?
Just listen to me for a second.
They're going to meet... how many minutes before they meet.
Let's wrap it up!
Yes, yes, yes.
Then maybe we can make it in time.
Yes, yes.
And a little bit of bjorn, a little bit of bjorn.
Bjorn.
Yes.
A-ding and B-ding are 5 km away from Biyorn.
Yes. Let's try something like that.
Yes.
Problem: A-dong and B-dong are 5 km apart.
Nishida-san walks 50 meters per minute from A-Chome.
If Ms. Y. Satoyoshi leaves at the same time from B-Chome by bicycle at 150 meters per minute, what will it be after how many minutes?
How many minutes will it be before the two meet?
Let's summarize!
OK.
I got it.
Finish!
Yes, I'm done. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. I would like to summarize Mr. Bjorns! The first time I had the opportunity to see Fate's Traveler live was when they performed for the first time,
It was the first time I saw Mr. Bjorns perform live.
At that time, how should I put it? I was so impressed by the high level of perfection from the very beginning,
You rehearse in the morning, don't you?
That's right.
It was amazing how quickly she could say her lines without biting her tongue,
I tend to bite my words even in everyday conversation,
I would chew my lines even in everyday conversation, but you always say long lines to the orchestra,
I think it's really amazing,
What I like about this song is that it has a great storyline,
I played the role of a traveler when I was in elementary school, but I couldn't do it at all,
I couldn't do it at all, even my mother couldn't do it,
I told my mother to be prepared when I was a traveler, because I was not good at it,
So when I first heard it, I felt very familiar with it,
So when I heard it for the first time, it sounded familiar.
Yes, it is. When do you use it? I was listening to it while thinking, "When do you use it?
I, Sakurai. I have watched the music video of "Seek yo Fate Travelers" many times.
I really want to listen to it over and over again.
I keep replaying the music video over and over again.
The members of the band actually reproduced the lyrics in the music video.
The scene where Nishida-san is walking, for example, is reproduced in the music video,
I thought it was very nice that they actually reproduced the scene.
I am sure.
Yes, it is.
The costumes are also very cute.
I understand.
They are cute, aren't they?
When I was with Miyano-san at the concert, I could hear the sound of rehearsals,
Every time I hear the sound of rehearsal, I wish I could see them again from the front,
So, I would like to look forward to that time when I have a chance to see the concert again.So, if I have a chance to see it again, I would like to enjoy it.
Yes, I will.
This is the vocal recording of Momohime Kiyono by Beyonds Motome yo... Unmei no Tabibito San.
Beyonds new single "Yume wo nakurenai yozora ni" (In the night sky where you can't even draw a dream) Now on sale
Take care of yourself and don't be too hard on yourself.
Here is the next one.
Tsubaki Factory Skip Skip Skip Vocal Recording
From Tsubaki Factory's latest single
Skip skip skip skip. Here is the vocal recording of Yumi Kasai.
I'll start with the A melody of the first verse,
It's a bit of a funky tune,
It needs a bouncy feel, so I'll try to sing it with a bit of a bouncy image.
Yes, I'll try to make it bouncy.
A light rain of luring water is falling A forecast of stars after this
Suddenly I'm sorry, I'll see you today, heart fluttering sound
Yes, it sounds good.
I'm sorry, I'll see you today" is a question mark.
It's a bit more nuanced.
Suddenly I'm sorry, I'll see you today
So the third string is a little breezy.
Suddenly I'm sorry, but I'll see you today.
Yes!
I understand.
It's a bit keyed up.
I want it to feel more like a line.
Yes!
A light rain is forecast for the stars.
I'm sorry to bother you... but I'll see you today.
I think it's good.
That's good.
That's good. That's good.
Thank you very much.
Let's go to B-mule.
The sound of a heartbeat
Even the dust before the wind is dancing Jump to your happiness
If you don't dance, we'll meet at the west exit gate and hurry up.
It's getting a little rockier or a little worse as we go into the second half of the show.
I'm still excited if you keep it a little breezier, but could you try a more breezy vector for the excitement?
Should I drop it at the beginning? No, you don't have to drop it. It's fine to start now, but your voice is getting to the point where it's like you're in a hurry to get there, so I don't think you should drop it.
I don't think we should go that fast.
Even the dust before the wind will dance.
We've got to dance.
OK!
Great. Today's nice.
What's up?
What's wrong? I just...
I ate a rice ball.
Is that so?
I just had work for Dacio.
I was so excited this morning.
It's still kind of nice.
It's good.
Good!
I've been hyped up since this morning.
That's right.
So you're feeling like you've got a good engine right now.
Yes, yes, yes. It's easier to speak up.
That's good.
It's like radio every time.
So you'll come after you work? Yes, that's right. And I'll ask the manager.
I'll ask the manager.
"Waku waku seduction, so very, very romance
Waiting for your heart to be in trouble WEEKEN NIGHT
Skip, skip, skip, skip
It's like a mix between my own voice and a fal
Romance
Lote and sote both romance
Let's try it once
And We can love a little bit longer
We can love
Like, like, like...
Yes, I can't do it!
Skip-skip-skip-skip.
Yeah, that's about it.
Skip-skip-skip-skip
And I think it's like, "I love you.
How does that sound?
Well, it's a boy saying it.
So, it's a boy saying "I love you" to someone as he passes by.
He says he's on the phone, so I guess he's saying it on the phone.
And the girl hears him say it.It's a situation where a girl hears about it, so...
Well, it's a boy.
Like a man? Like a man, but not like I'm taking you to the station.
Not like that? More casual.
I love you. I don't think I'm being serious.
More casual. I love you. I love you.
I'll give it a try.
I love you.
A little bit.
That's what I mean.
Maybe a little more boyish.
I love you.
That camera diagonally in front of you.
Camera?
That one! The up-camera camera.
Face it.
I love you.
Huh?
Keep looking forward to the sound of our voices passing each other.
Yes, ma'am.
Poof.
I love you.
Okay, let's do it!
Let's do it!
Here you go!
They're all going to look up.
I love you.
Yes, I watched the VTR, and I thought it was very instructive to see the recording process,
I thought it was very wonderful that Mr. Kasai looked so happy and sang with a big smile in accordance with the song,
I was listening to the song while thinking that it seemed to be quite difficult for me.
I have received a lot of lines from her before, and I have never received lines from Morning Musume. I had received lines from Morning Musume,
It was really difficult to get the nuance of the lines, so I tried to imitate, or at least refer to, the various members of the group who had come before me,
The "I love you so much" line was so cute, it made me gasp.
I understand.
It was so cute.
I like the way Yuri Kasai plays with OK!
When I watched the VTR, the title of the song was "skip-skip-skip-skip,
The rhythm of the song sounded like they were holding hands and skipping together,
It felt really good to my ears and made me want to skip along with them.
That's true. That song really makes me want to skip along with them.
So I will study a lot and do my best so that I can skip along with you.
That's all for Tsubaki Factory Skip Skip Skip Vocal Recording by Yuri Kasai.
Hello! I'm Yasuzaki. I'm Mari Yaguchi.
So, this year is the 25th anniversary of Hello Project,
We're going to have an event!
Yay!
The name of the event is "Morning Musume. 2nd term Mari Anzaki Yaguchi presents Mari Yaguchi 2!
Well, I can't tell you what it's going to be about, but I can tell you that we've already decided on a few things, and we're looking forward to having fun!
I can't tell you what it's going to be about, but I can tell you that it's going to be a fun concert,
How do you feel about the 25th anniversary of Hello Project? How is it going, Kei-chan?
It seems like no time has passed. 25 years have already passed,
I think the fans are growing old together with me.
What was the most memorable moment for you?
The live performance at Sun Plaza in May?
Hello Productions. I was physically exhausted at that time.
Yes, it was. But it was really great to see all the fans so early in the new year.
That's for sure. Well, we still do countdowns and so on,
I think it is one of the great things about Hello Project that we can start the new year with our fans.
This year's event will be held on the 26th of May,
The event will be held on May 26th, one day before our second term members joined the project,
The place is, let's meet in Yurakucho.
Let's meet.
We are going to have an event at Aisousho in Yurakucho, on the second floor.
There are other members this time, and we are going to have a fun event with junior members,
From among the Halo Pro graduates, we have Katsuta-chan, and from the current members, Tsubaki Fuka.
And from the current members, Akiyama from Tsubaki Factory, Hirai from BEYOOOOONDS.
Hirai from BEYOOOOONDS. And Kitahara from Ochanoma.
And from Upga2, we have Kaji-chan.
Kajishima-chan, right?
Kaji-chan, right? Will you wipe it with your peacoder nose?
Oh, you'll bring it.
Please bring it.
I'm looking forward to it.
So, it seems like we don't have anything in common, but actually, we do.
Yes, we do.
We are second-term members, and the members who are going to be with us on stage this time also joined the group later, so we have something in common,
So, yes.
I hope we can talk about all kinds of things on stage.
Isn't this the first time for you to hold such an event?
Yes, it is.Yes, I think so.
I think it will be a very valuable time,
I'm excited.
We will also draw out a lot of things from the seniors,
Yes, we have a professional MC.
No, no, we have a professional MC.
Yes, we do.
Kaja-kun will do it for us.
That's right.
So I hope we can talk about the second term and the additional members together.
Also, I would like to sing a song.
That's the point.
At first, I thought it would be a talk event,
But then I got a little greedy,
I was a little greedy, and I said, "Yes, I'll do a few songs.
I'll do a few songs.
Was it just singing?
Just singing?
What are you going to do? Dance?
Dancing.
You can do that?
Yes, I do.
Well, I'll learn a lot from the younger members,
I hope we can make not only our songs, but also their songs.
I am not sure if I will be able to do it. I am not sure if I will be able to remember them.
We have one song that has been decided, but the choreography has not yet been included.
Yes, that's right. Will I be able to dance prettily?
Will I be able to dance prettily?
No, please look at me warmly.
It's the 25th anniversary.
But since it's our 25th anniversary, I'd like to enjoy performing with you,
And this time, if I wear a mask, I can speak,
I am very happy.
I am sure everyone has been waiting for that moment.
I'm glad.
Are you all right? How's your throat?
Use your abs and your throat already.
Please do me a favor. Let me hear it. It's been a while since I heard your voices.
I would like you to get excited about the exciting songs from now on,
Please get yourself in shape now.
Please, we will be doing this on May 26th, so please look forward to it everyone.
Let's work together!
So, first of all, let's go to the A melody!
Yes, sir.
Well, I'm going to dryly say a confident con.
What shall we do, stop at the runway? Or do we go all the way to Dynamite?
Oh, I don't know.
I'll go for a spin.
You want to go for a spin?
Um, yes.
Okay, let's start with A melody to Dynamite.
Okay.
It's obvious you're scared. Just watch me.
I'm gonna take my best step. This is my runway.
I said, hugging my unsure shoulders, "I'm boring.
I'm a bore, I'm a bore, I'm a bore, I'm a bore, I'm a bore, I'm a bore, I'm a bore, I'm a bore
I'm selfish, I'm free, I'm free, I'm hupper dynamite
So this is my runway now, right?
Yes, sir.
It's a full-on runway
I want to look like I'm walking around all dressed up.
Yes.
More like that.
I don't mean that you should sing to the top of your lungs, but...
But you can be more flamboyant.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mm-hm.
So like that.
Okay.
Let it all out.
Okay, let's try one more time.
Let's do it again.
He's so thirsty for confidence. He's so boring.
He's so scared, it's obvious. Just watch.
I'm taking my best steps This is my runway
I've been hugging his insecure shoulder I'm so boring
I'm boring I'm boring I'm boring I'm boring I'm boring I'm boring I'm boring I'm boring I'm boring I'm boring
I want to be spoiled sometimes I want to be selfish I want to be free to do what I want I want to be hupper dynamite
Oh, that's good, isn't it? It's funny.
I thought it was really funny when he said "on the runway".I thought it was really funny when he said that he was on the runway.
But that video in the first half...
Her confidence is so cute!
I thought it was a waste that the word "cute" was turned upside down for a moment when she said it.
I thought it was a waste of time.
Let's do the first half again.
He's so thirsty for confidence scams. He's so boring.
He's so scared, it's obvious. Just watch.
I'm taking my best steps. This is my runway.
It's fine, right?
Then I'll be right here, like this, and you'll be good to go.
Oh, my God.
Cool girl, cute girl.
Let's do it this way.
Strong part, fragile part
I'll be valence
You have to love them all. All of them.
Yes, yes, yes.
You know that cool girl who comes in here?
Like this...
I'll show you what I'm talking about.
I'll show you...
Um...
If I go here earlier...
Of course I'll find you
It's a different guy singing.
I'm going to go with the face habit one more time, so I'd better go in a little stronger.
OK.
And then, now you're just rusty.
OK, I'm going to go to the chorus.
OK, OK, I guess that's it then.
Okay, that's it then.
Okay. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Yes, this song is a unit song by three members, Ms. Rikako Sasaki, Mr. Yumoi Kamikoguri, and Ms. Rin Kawahara,
When I heard this song for the first time, I thought it was really cool.
When I first heard this song, I thought it was really cool, or it really had a runway feel to it,
She sang with nuance and her facial expressions were really cool, and they were also attached to her singing,
I really wanted to listen to the song with earphones and feel like I was on the runway.
Yes, I, Sakurai, was really impressed with the atmosphere of this song, which is a cool song for a three-person unit.
I thought it was a very cool song, and I thought you really matched the atmosphere of the song.
I was thinking that when I saw how you were recording the vocals,
The sound is really cool. I would love to hear it at the concert,
I am sure that fans would also like to hear it in a concert venue with perfect acoustics,
I'm really looking forward to having the chance to hear it in the future.
That's all for now, here is the vocal recording of Rikako Sasaki, the top singer of Angulum.
Angulum's new album "Pick Club! Now on sale!
Let's take it easy today.
It's time to say goodbye to the up-cam that Arisaha Ichika and Rio Sakurai have brought you.
I've seen a lot of videos this time, but this is the first time for me to mention that this is my first appearance as an MC for up-cam,
I have been watching the videos of the three MC's for the first time, and I have to admit that this is the first time for me to mention this, but I feel that up-cam is a YouTube channel where I can learn a lot of things,
This time, I was able to watch the videos of the three performers, and I was able to see Rikako Sasaki's vocal recording,
I was able to see Rikako Sasaki's vocal recording, which is a unit song, right? I think that unit songs are songs that allow us to see the members more clearly.
I think that unit songs are a great way to get to know the members better. I often learn a lot from them,
I love this unit song very much. That's why we were given the opportunity to see the top of the band this time, and we found many good points.
I found many good points in it, so I am really looking forward to seeing them at the concert.
I, Arisa, was impressed by Yumi Kasai's vocal recording of "Skip Skip Skip,
I was impressed by the way she sang the song as if she was the main character of the song,
I was also impressed by the way she sang as if she was the main character of the song. She looked like an actress when she sang, and I thought her singing was really good.
Akukami will take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the up-front group.
Please subscribe to our channel to get a glimpse into the behind-the-scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
This time, Akkami is with Arisa Aoi Chika of Juice Juice and Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume. 23's Rio Sakurai. Good bye.
Next time on Akkami,
BEYOOOOONDS's recording of "Yume wo nakurenai yozora ni" (I can't even draw a dream in the night sky),
and Big Love, Angulum's latest album,
I want to destroy it! from Angelem's latest album, Big Love.
Please look forward to it!
Please subscribe to our channel!